Guide to the Newport Restoration Foundation Records, 1968-1999 (bulk 1968-1982) RL.01440
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Architectural Records, 1968-1970, 1986 and undated
  - 41 Mary Street Vertical Section, Placement of 2nd level on Second Floor. Steven Laurin. [1977]. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF6)
  - Coggeshall House-66 William St. Site Plan (18 sheets). Steven Laurin. 1977 Mar 2. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF7)